END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

Wrocisław font, designed by Adam Rucki (http://airdesign.pl)

CONDITIONS

1. The font is free for personal use, that include:
- work where you are not paid for your services, and where there is no monetary benefit to any part as a result of using the font,
- student work, both school assignments and self initiated projects, as long as you are not paid for your services, and where there is no monetary benefit to any part as a result of using the font.

2. If you want to use this font for commercial activity, contact the author in order to purchase it.

3. The font may freely be copied and passed along to other individuals for private use as its original downloadable zip-file, that includes the font files and this End User License Agreement. It may not be sold or published without written permission by its author.

4. The font may not be modified, altered, adapted or built upon without written permission by its author. This pertains all files within the downloadable font zip-file.

DISCLAIMER

The font is provided "as is", without warranty of any kind, express or implied, including but not limited to any warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and noninfringement of copyright, patent, trademark, or other right. In no event shall the copyright holder be liable for any claim, damages or other liability, including any general, special, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, whether in an action of contract, tort or otherwise, arising from, out of the use or inability to use the font software or from other dealings in the font software.

By using the given typeface you agree to the terms of this license.